

Mohit Tayal

Sr. Analyst

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/mohit2812/

Profile

I, Mohit Tayal working as a Sr. Analyst in Capgemini Pvt. Ltd. India. Two times awarded as a Rising Star for being one of the best employee within a project. I am having nearly 1 year and 11 months of work experience in pharma domain and having functional and technical knowledge on Informatica Power Centre, Oracle SQL Database, Apex and My Reporting Platforms, writing Automation Scripts, having good Problem Solving abilities and ability to take responsibilities until the challenges faced are fulfilled.

Professional Experience

Sr. Analyst, *Capgemini Pvt. Ltd.*

01/2023 - present

- Attending WSR calls with the System Leads to keep the track on the performance of the team working under EMEA region for German clients.
- Bangalore (WFH), India
- Reviewed project documentation and made important changes to match updates to project type.
- Developed ETL enhancement feature requests to improve product functionality and extend performance..
- Investigated application issues, identified causes and initiated troubleshooting methods for intermediate resolution.
- Worked deeply with oracle database packages, procedures, triggers, views, tables. Backtracking tables, understanding dataflow architecture and finding the bug causing the issue within the database.

Analyst, Capqemini Pvt. Ltd.

06/2021 - 12/2022

Bangalore (WFH), India

- Service monitoring and production support.
- Working with multiple upstream and downstream.
- Involved in resolving critical issues effectively and efficiently on time.
- Query tuning, fixing performance issues in batch jobs.
- Diagnosing and correcting error and faults in application.
- Performing regular data loads and monitoring the performance of the loads to successfully complete without any issues.

Internship Trainee, Lotus Quality Assurance

01/2020 - 03/2020

- Worked as full stack developer and helped organization to make an attractive registration page.
- Also worked on few projects like making a platform where you can shop for posters online and also made a chess game using oops functions like inheritance, abstraction etc.

Hanoi, Vietnam

Education

BTech. (CSE), Chandigarh Engineering College SGPA - 7.68

07/2017 – 07/2021 Landran, Punjab

Skills

Oracle DBA Data Analysis	• • • •	Informatica Powercentre	• • • • •
	• • • • •	Business Analysis	• • • • •
Project Management	• • • • •	Incident Management	• • • • •
Team Leadership	• • • • •	Documentation	• • • • •

Certificates

- Agile Software Development
- E-Commerce Developer (FDR)
- Presentation Skills
- Relational Database Design
- Business Intelligence
- Writing Skills

- Informatica Power Center
- Difficult Interactions
- Web Developer

Languages

• English

• Hindi

Punjabi